export const UnCon = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "βαίνω",
    back: ["I Go", "First Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "βαίνεις",
    back: ["You Go", "Second Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "βαίνει",
    back: ["He/She/it Goes", "First Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "βαίνομεν",
    back: ["We Go", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "βαίνετε",
    back: ["You Go", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "βαίνοθσι(ν)",
    back: ["They Go", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  }
];

export const ACon = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "ὁρῶ",
    back: ["I See", "First Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "ὁρᾷς",
    back: ["You See", "Second Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "ὁρᾷ",
    back: ["He/She/It Sees", "Third Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "ὁρῶμεν",
    back: ["We See", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "ὁρᾶτε",
    back: ["You See", "Second Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "ὁρῶσι(ν)",
    back: ["They See", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  }
];

export const ECon = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "ποιῶ",
    back: ["I Do", "First Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "ποιεῖς",
    back: ["You Do", "Second Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "ποιεῖ",
    back: ["He/She/It Does", "Third Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "ποιοῦμεν",
    back: ["We Do", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "ποιεῖτε",
    back: ["You Do", "Second Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "ποιοῦσι(ν)",
    back: ["They See", "Third Person", "(pl)"]
  }
];

export const OCon = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "δηλῶ",
    back: ["I Show", "First Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "δηλοῖς",
    back: ["You Show", "Second Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "δηλοῖ",
    back: ["He/She/It Sees", "Third Person", "(s)"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "δηλοῦμεν",
    back: ["We See", "First Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "δηλοῦτε",
    back: ["You See", "Second Person", "(pl)"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "δηλοῦσι(ν)",
    back: ["They See", "Third Person", "(pl)"]
  }
];
